DJ Got Us Fallin In Love
压制:随Feng
歌手：Usher & Pitbull
Yeah man
是啊兄弟
So we back in the club
我们又回到了夜店
Get that bodies rockin from side to side (side to side)
大家的身体一起左右摇摆起来
Thank God the week is done
感谢上帝又到了周末
I feel like a zombie gone back to life (back to life)
我感觉像是僵尸重获新生
Hands up
举起双手
and suddenly we all got our hands up
瞬间大家都举起的双手
No control of my body
身体似乎不再受控制
Ain't I seen you before
以前我见过你么
I think I remember those
我认为我记得
eyes,eyes,eyes(ei...)
你的眼神...
Cause baby tonight
宝贝 因为今晚
The DJ got us falling in love again
DJ让我们再次相爱
Yeah, baby tonight
耶 宝贝 今晚
The DJ got us falling in love again
DJ让我们再次相爱
So dance, dance, like it's the last
那就跳舞 就好像
last night of your life, life
今晚是生命中的最后一晚
Gonna get you right
得让你进入正轨
Cause baby tonight
宝贝 因为今晚
The DJ got us falling in love again
DJ让我们再次相爱
Keep downing drinks like this
不停的像这样喝着酒
Not tomorrow that just right now
我说的不是明天 而是现在
now, now, now, now, now, now
现在...
Gonna set the roof on fire
让我们把屋顶点燃
Gonna burn this mother fucker
把整座大楼烧毁
down, down, down, down, down, down
烧毁...
Hands up
举起双手
when the music drops
音乐一响
We both put our hands up
双手举高
Put your hands on my body
把手放在我的身上
Swear I seen you before
我发誓我曾见过你
I think I remember those
我想我记得
eyes,eyes,eyes(ei...)
你的眼神
Cause baby tonight
宝贝 因为今晚
The DJ got us falling in love again
DJ让我们再次相爱
Yeah, baby tonight
耶 宝贝 今晚
The DJ got us falling in love again
DJ让我们再次相爱
So dance, dance, like it's the last
那就跳舞 就好像
last night of your life, life
今晚是生命中的最后一晚
Gonna get you right
得让你进入正轨
Cause baby tonight
宝贝 因为今晚
The DJ got us falling in love again
DJ让我们再次相爱
You know evil, speak no evil, see no evil
你知道什么是邪恶 但从你的眼神和话语中我看不到邪恶
Get it baby, hope you catch that GO
快来 宝贝 我希望你还能赶上
That's how we roll
我们就是如此
My life is a movie and you just TIVO
我的生活就像一场电影 而你的像是录影机
Mami got me switchin like a dreadlock
美女让我像满头辫子一样摇摆
She don't wrestle but I got her in a headlock
她不是个摔跤手 但我还是用双腿夹住她的头
Yabadabadoo make her bedrock- mami on fire, red hot
哦也哦也 让她在床上颤动 她太火太辣了
badabingbadaboom Mr. Worldwide as I step in the room
badabingbadaboom 世界知名先生走进了房间
I'm a hustler baby
宝贝 我可是个赚钱机器
But that you knew and tonight it's just me and you
你知道的 今晚将会是我们两个的世界
Cause baby tonight
宝贝 因为今晚
The DJ got us falling in love again
DJ让我们再次相爱
Yeah, baby tonight
耶 宝贝 今晚
The DJ got us falling in love
DJ让我们再次相爱
So dance, dance, like it's the last
那就跳舞 就好像
last night of your life, life
今晚是生命中的最后一晚
Gonna get you right
得让你进入正轨
Cause baby tonight
宝贝 因为今晚
The DJ got us falling in love again
DJ让我们再次相爱
Yeah, baby tonight
耶 宝贝 今晚
The DJ got us falling in love again
DJ让我们再次相爱
So dance, dance, like it's the last
那就跳舞 就好像
last night of your life, life
今晚是生命中的最后一晚
Gonna get you right
得让你进入正轨
Cause baby tonight
宝贝 因为今晚
The DJ got us falling in love again
DJ让我们再次相爱
压制:随Feng
Yeah, thank you DJ haha
耶 宝贝 今晚